[
    {
        "question": "what is the name ",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.9794179797172546,
                "answer": "AMRITPAL SINGH",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 1
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the complete gmail id?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.6491357684135437,
                "answer": "amritpalsingh1018@gmail.com",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 6
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the telephone number?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 4.594129521251489e-09,
                "answer": "11/2021 - 07/2023.",
                "start": 119,
                "end": 121
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the  LinkedIn ID ?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.31158366799354553,
                "answer": "+1(226) 961-9248",
                "start": 3,
                "end": 4
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did they work in the latest experience?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.3177016079425812,
                "answer": "Mohali, India",
                "start": 123,
                "end": 124
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the name of company they worked in the experience section",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.9976115822792053,
                "answer": "AMRITPAL SINGH",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 1
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what are the dates mention in the latest company in the experience",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.9992569088935852,
                "answer": "11/2021 - 07/2023.",
                "start": 119,
                "end": 121
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is work done in the latest experience?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.11014430969953537,
                "answer": "gain practical experience and learn from industry professionals.",
                "start": 105,
                "end": 112
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what are all the tasks done in the latest experince?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.005814665462821722,
                "answer": "data cleansing and formatting",
                "start": 212,
                "end": 215
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is name of the university  DURING bachelors?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.9902943968772888,
                "answer": "St. Clair",
                "start": 28,
                "end": 29
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the bachelors's course?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.09763967990875244,
                "answer": "Aspiring Data Scientist,",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 17
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is name of the university  DURING masters?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.056158971041440964,
                "answer": "St. Clair",
                "start": 28,
                "end": 29
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the masters's course?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.01068041566759348,
                "answer": "Post-Graduation in Data Analytics",
                "start": 21,
                "end": 24
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is name of the college or university of latest education?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.8897513151168823,
                "answer": "St. Clair College of Applied Arts & Technology.",
                "start": 28,
                "end": 35
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the latest course ?",
        "answer": [
            {
                "score": 0.9596719145774841,
                "answer": "data science",
                "start": 60,
                "end": 61
            }
        ],
        "page": 1
    }
]